PAUL LEWIS: Hello, and welcome to this Supercharged TL;DW.
欢迎使用此Supercharged TL; DW
Last time, [? Sermer ?] and I made an accordion.
上一次我和Surma制作了手风琴。
Not the musical kind. [ACCORDION NOISES] That
不是乐器。
No, instead, what we made was a UI element.
相反，我们创建了一个小部件。
Let's take a look at what we made.
让我们看看我们做了什么。
So you can see on screen here, we
正如您在此处的屏幕上看到的那样，
have a bunch of panels-- one, two, three.
我们有一个，两个，三个面板。
And you can see that they're sliding up and down.
您会看到它们在上下滑动。
Now you can also use your keyboard as well.
您也可以使用键盘。
Tab, and arrow keys, and so forth as well.
Tab键和方向键。
Let's also look at the performance side.
让我们看一下性能方面。
I've the timeline here in Dev Tools open.
您已经在开发人员工具中打开了时间表。
If I click around these panels, you'll
如果单击这些面板
see that each one of those clicks, there's an animation.
您会发现，每次单击都会产生动静。
And if we zoom in, it's a comfortable 60 frames a second.
如果放大，则会发现每秒60帧。
Lovely and green.
美丽而绿色。
No red markers there.
没有红色标记。
Working really well.
运作良好。
So how do we make it?
那么我们如何做到呢？
Well, as we get into that, of course,
我们解释这种方法
there's only one place to go for this discussion.
有一个地方要谈。
Yes.
是的是的
Theory Corner.
“理论理论”。
Hello, my friends.
你好我的朋友们。
Welcome to Theory Corner.
欢迎来到理论理论。
Now, here's our set this time.
这是我们这次的基础。
We have a bunch of panels.
我们有一系列的绘画。
And, by default, what we're going to do
默认情况下，我们要做的是
is we're going to leave those well alone.
是我们将不理会它。
Sounds odd.
看起来很奇怪。
But if JavaScript doesn't run, we
但是如果JavaScript不起作用，
don't want to lose this content.
我们不想丢失此内容。
So we're going to style based on the fact
因此，我们将基于
that JavaScript is running.
JavaScript可以正常工作。
So if JavaScript isn't running for some reason,
如果JavaScript由于某种原因无法正常工作，
these panels will just stack up.
这些面板将形成一个堆栈。
OK?
对不对
If JavaScript is running, we're going
如果JavaScript有效，我们将
to set a flag on the element, which
标记元素
is going to cause the panels to rejig into this format, where
这将使绘画以这种方式重新组合
we have them kind of stacked up like this.
我们以这种方式使它们成为同义词。
And the other things that we need to do
我们需要做的另一件事是
is, as you click on a panel header,
然后按下面板的顶部，
we're going to slide that panel into place.
我们将其滑动到正确的位置。
For this to also work, we want to make sure
为了使这种方法也能正常工作，我们必须确保
that all content that's kind of outside this box is hidden.
隐藏在此框之外的所有内容。
So we use overflow:hidden.
因此，我们将使用溢出：隐藏。
And we want to make sure that the content itself only
我们要确保内容相同
takes up this amount of room.
只需要这么多。
And anything that's longer than that would need a scroll bar.
超过此长度将需要移动磁带。
Fair enough.
这很方便。
OK.
让我们看看编程的内容。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Have you ever noticed how you never have
你有没有注意到手风琴
heavy metal and an accordion?
和“重金属”不在一起。
So let's look at the code itself.
让我们看一下符号本身。
Now, the code is quite interesting overall.
该符号通常很有趣。
And if you've got time, definitely
如果有时间
watch that Livestream.
观看直播。
It's about an hour long, but there's bugs
大约一个小时的长度，但是有错误
and there's loads of stuff and loads of discussion.
还有很多事情和讨论。
Some brilliant questions from the people
人类的聪明问题
who are watching Livestream, so it's really worth
他们看直播，所以值得
catching that if you can.
如果可以，请继续。
But there are main things that we can dive into
但是有些基本的东西我们可以更深入地研究
and actually have a proper look at.
仔细看一下它们。
And the main thing that I think we'll start with
我们将要开始的最基本的事情
is the attached call back.
是“附加回电”。
We're using custom elements here for the accordion
我们在这里将自定义元素用于手风琴和模板。
You see that actually in the HTML.
您将在HTML中看到这一点。
Let's have a look there quickly.
让我们快速浏览一下。
There's the accordion.
这是手风琴。
And then each of those panes is in there with a header
这些模板中的每个模板都有一个头部按钮
button and the content itself.
和内容本身。
So let's look at the accordion again.
让我们再次看一下手风琴。
So when it gets attached, what we do
安装后，我们会做
is we ask for all the panes, and then
是我们会询问所有模板，然后
we calculate the geometries.
我们计算工程流程。
And the geometries is basically how tall is the header.
操作只是头的长度。
OK?
对不对
And then we figure out the available height
然后我们将计算可用长度
based on the total height of the accordion minus the number
从负手风琴的总长度开始
of headers we've got.
我们有多少个头。
And that's the amount of content space that we've got.
这就是我们有多少内容。
When we move the panels around and we set up
然后我们移动盘子并调整所有东西，
everything, what we want to do is
我们要做的是
we want to make sure that we reset the pane content height
我们要确保返回内容长度值
to be that available height.
成为可用长度。
So you see over there, the flower?
如您所见，
That's the available height.
这是可用长度所在的位置。
That's where that bit is.
那部分在哪里。
So we want to make sure that all our panes have
我们要确保我们所有的模板都有
that available height.
那是可用的长度。
Perfect.
理想的。
When we see a pane that has the area expanded attribute,
当我们看到具有“区域扩展”功能的模板时，
then we jump down.
然后我们下去。
Because that's the expanded pane.
因为这是扩展模板。
So we need to make sure that all of the other content
我们必须确保所有其他内容在其下都是同义词。
Fair enough.
很方便
All good.
一切都很好。
So we've done that, and the calculate geometries,
在工程计算中，我们这样做是“移动面板”，
move panels.
然后我们准备了一些“事件监听器”
for handling clicks and handling other things.
处理点击和其他事情。
And then we basically set this attribute, which is active.
然后我们设置此功能，将其激活。
And that means that the accordion is now
这意味着手风琴现在
ready for business.
准备工作。
And we can get going.
我们可以继续。
But maybe you're wondering how, in fact, do
您可能想知道如何
you do the bit where you click on a header
单击顶部的部分
or you select it with a keyboard and hit Enter.
或者使用键盘选择它，然后按Enter。
What happens then?
那会发生什么呢？
Glad you asked.
感谢您的询问。
Here to answer your questions indeed.
在这里肯定可以回答您的问题。
So we have to jump over to the SC pane JavaScript for that.
为此，我们必须跳转到JavaScript的JavaScript模板。
And all we have in here, really apart from a couple of getters,
除了一些吸气剂，我们在这里拥有的一切，
is this attach callback.
这是附加回调。
And when you click on the header inside one of the panes,
当您将头压入其中一个模具中时，
we dispatch a custom event.
我们将发起一个特别活动。
Now, if you've never come across custom events before,
如果您以前从未谈论过私人活动，
they're brilliant.
他们很棒。
What they do is they act like a normal event,
他们所做的就是像任何普通事件一样出现
except that you get to name it and you get to set things
除了可以命名和调整内容
like whether it bubbles, or it's cancellable,
就像您可以“冒泡”或“取消”一样，
all that kind stuff.
依此类推。
Here we're using one called Panel Change.
在这里，我们使用一种称为“面板更改”的面板。
And we're going to say that it's bubbling up
我们会说气泡会增加
through the dom, which is great because we want to delegate
通过DOM，这很棒，因为我们想代表
the handling of the panel change up to the accordion element
将模板更改处理为手风琴元素本身。
Which you will notice in the event listeners.
这是您在“事件侦听器”中会注意到的。
Event listeners here, there's this panel change.
这是活动的讲台，在这里是绘画的变化。
Same name, great.
同一个名字，很棒。
And then there's this stop on panel change, which
然后这是绘画变化的停顿，
involves basically stepping through all
它基本上包括逐步
the available panes, turn them all to collapse,
所有可用的模板，将它们变成收缩状态，
and then finding the one that you actually selected,
然后搜索您选择的模板，
and telling that one to expand.
并使其扩展。
Last but not least, we then call Move Panels again.
最后但并非最不重要的一点，我们再次调用“移动面板”。
And Move Panels is going to basically tell all the panels
移动面板将说明所有模板的基础
where they should be.
儿子，她一定是。
And, basically, by the power of transitions on transforms,
谢谢实用程序
what will happen is, as you tell a pane to be translate y, 200
将会发生什么，您将对在y轴上拉动200像素的模板说
pixels, it's going to go up down the screen, which ultimately
它会在屏幕上消失，最终
gives you the effect that we saw before.
它会为您带来我们以前见过的效果。
So we're basically sliding panels around the screen.
因此，我们基本上是在屏幕上滑动模板。
Performed really well.
通过很好的表现。
So there you have it.
所以您在这里已经知道。
A prototype of an accordion that is performance and has
我必须演奏的手风琴的原型
a really good foundation for something like accessibility.
很好的基础，例如到来。
Now don't forget that you can subscribe to the channel,
别忘了您可以订阅该频道，
and you can watch the Livestream.
并观看直播。
It's about an hour long, but there's
大约一个小时
loads in there-- great discussions, bugs, bug fixes,
但是到处都是事物，辩论，错误和修正
whole heap of things.
大范围。
And I will catch you, of course, next time.
当然我下次见。
Now, I know it looks a bit strange.
我知道这听起来很奇怪。
Just click it and subscribe.
只需单击并订阅。
Also Livestream, over there, that's worth watching, bugs
还有现场直播，值得一看，
and everything.
错误等